Well, does it have a pro option as well?
I'm not aware.
So let's see, let me search, deep seek chatbot pro pricing.
Models and pricing, ah, it's for the API.
But I assume that deep seek itself does not
have any kind of pro option.
So this is all you get.
And I think it comes with no limitations of chatting.
So let me, let again ask itself.
So let's say I couldn't find no pro or premium plans
for you deep seek chatbots.
I wanted to know if your free and with no chatting
limitations for the free account, are you?
And let's see what it answers.
Yes, so as you see, good news.
Yes, I'm completely free.
And there are no chatting limitations for the free account.
Well, that's perfect, right?
So we don't have a lot of options over here,
but we have free unlimited chatting, you know?
So deep seek doesn't currently offer any pro or premium plans.
And what you see is what you get.
And it's all free, perfect.
But as you see, yes, the pricing stuff
was for the API stuff, you know?
So it's API documentation of the deep seek.
But deep seek itself is a free chatbot that you can use.
It seems like it's unlimitedly free for now.